{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_10_2QGJ81",
                "player_12_2QGJ81"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                10,
                12
            ],
            "animation": [
                "pick_up",
                "liedown"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    13754.839,
                    -1114.376,
                    -12713.017,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    13749.317,
                    -1936.059,
                    -12713.225,
                    0,
                    41.00280704943427,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "drone": {
            "name": [
                "drone_0_2QGJ81"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0
            ],
            "animation": [
                "none"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Aerial drone with a black and white frame, dual rotors, and a streamlined design."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    13645.365,
                    -1264.48,
                    -12512.956,
                    0,
                    -24.82642485201339,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            13683.832,
            -1351.302,
            -12712.956
        ],
        "sample_radius": 788.4123610487801
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "drone"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            13704.721,
            -554.913,
            -12713.161,
            0,
            -89.23561907513343,
            0
        ],
        [
            13534.663,
            -1414.368,
            -12712.956,
            0,
            -7.499003718729583,
            0
        ],
        [
            13870.172,
            -2173.798,
            -12710.281,
            0,
            101.80093355828124,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, the_man_in_grey_suit or White_Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. White_Drone"
                ],
                "answer": "B. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to White_Drone, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many people are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are holding an object?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many drones can be seen in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many bald individuals are depicted in the scene?",
                "answer": "zero"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many men are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many individuals are sprawled and still on the ground?",
                "answer": "one"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man wearing a maroon polo shirt and beige pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding an object",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding an object"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man wearing a gray suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. liedown",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "B. liedown"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the White Drone relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Slightly below and to the back-right of",
                    "B. Slightly above and to the front-left of",
                    "C. Directly in front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Slightly above and to the front-left of"
            }
        }
    }
}